There is something under the ice…
Black Mountain Side is a thriller, horror, mystery
film directed by Nick Szostakiwskyj.
A group of archaeologists working in Northern Canada uncover a strange
structure dating over ten thousand years before the present.
The team soon finds themselves isolated when their communication
systems fail and they begin to feel the effects of solitude.
Jensen, played by Shane Twerdun.
Professor Piers Olsen, played by Michael Dickson.
Francis Månro, played by Carl Toftfelt.
Robert Michael Giles, played by Marc Anthony Williams.
Drew McNaughton, played by Timothy Lyle.
Steven Wells, played by Steven Bradley.
Black Mountain Side is a 2014 Canadian indie horror thriller written and directed by Nick Szostakiwskyj and starring Shane
Twerdun, Michael Dickson, Carl Toftfelt, Marc Anthony Williams, Andrew Moxham, Timothy Lyle, and Steve Bradley.
It was the first film released by the Canadian production
company A Farewell To Kings Entertainment Company.
The film centers upon a group of archaeologists who
discover an ancient structure in the Arctic.
The film explores themes of suicide, canada, isolation, winter, amputation.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.